غ~
ready!
!
fight.
̰ ϴ
this is terrible.
ִ ̾
in the best
possible way.
˰ ־
i know.
ũƾ ̰ſ ؼ
kristen told me about it.
иϰ ο Ϻ ũ ϴ
apparently bug fighting
is huge in japan.
׵ ΰ Ȯ
pretty sure it's
their national pastime.
Ÿ 븦 ̰ ־
that tarantula is
killin' it right now.
׷. ٿ ġŲ ΰ ڴ
ʵ ?
yeah. i'm gonna
go get some chicken fingers
from the snack bar. you want?
ȵ, ȵ, ٷ! ϴ ž?
ḻ ġڴ
no, no, wait! what are
you doing? you're gonna
miss the end.
? Ƴ, Ƴ, Ƴ
what? no, no, no.
ð ð
̺Ʈ
i'll be back in time
for the main event--
 Ͱ Ŷ
some weird lobster creature
fighting a centipede.
û ܿ
super gross.
ٽ ð
be back.
ǰ մ
very funny.
, !
sock, stop!
øԷ ī޶ űϴ
we move in on sam oliver,
ȣ ϰ..
curious...
ȥ..
confused...
׸ ..
and now...
Ű ...
irritated.
!
, ̺, ̰
ha ha ha ha!
oh, man, this is amazing.
չٴڿ °
fits right in the palm
of your hand
׸ ػ󵵴..
ȹϱ
and the resolution,
unbelievable.
, ī޶ ְŵ
yes. i've seen
a video camera before.
, ׷ ̰ ?
ah, but have you
seen this?
߿! ! !
please! help me! please!
̰ ۵ϴ ǰ?
is this thing
working?
װ ?
what was that?
, ׳ ۰Ÿ ־
oh, i'm just futzin' around,
you know,
ī޶ ۵ ˾ƺ
tryin' to get
the hang of the camera.
ƴ, ƴ. ſ
װ ?
no, no. that thing,
what was it?
, ϰ ȥ
ī
oh, that's your latest soul,
mordecai nash,
real nasty piece of work.
״ ҷ̰ ߾
he used to lure people
to the dove hollow silver mine,
׵鿡 ڷ ְڴٰ ϸ鼭
promising them
to strike it rich.
׷ ׵ ̰ ѾҾ
then he'd kill 'em
and take their money.
׷ װ ٽ Գ ..
so he's back as that...
˼ ް?
tentacle thing?
״ 
־
he's got his hands
on everything in dove hollow,
װ ׷ ó
just like he did in life.
ϰ ű ,
i want you to get
out there, sammy.
ȥ ٶ
i want you to grab
that guy a.s.a.p.
ϴ ް
just look at it
as a working vacation.
Ƹ ̰ŵ
you know, it's a beautiful
little town.
ϰ
see for yourself.
= =
wondrous
dove hollow
׷,
all right.
, ű ǰڳ׿
well, if i have
to go out there,
ص ֵ
maybe i could take andi
and the guys,
ڵ ǰڳ׿
make a road trip
out of it.
׷
there you go.
ž
that would be great.
, ̽ũ ü ־
now, here's a little cherry
for your sundae.
׸ ž
you're gonna love
this vessel.
̰ ϱ ų ׷ ?
is that badass or what?
ȥ ʿ䵵
you don't even have to
get close to the thing.
װ
Ƽ Ǵ ž
you just lob that baby
and watch the party.
ƿ, ׷
̰ ڳ׿
ok, yeah.
this could be good.
ް
little vacation.
̺Ʈ ģ ž?
i miss the main event?
, һ
oh, my god.
! ! !
help me! please! aah!
, 츮 ̶ Ŷ ϴ
Ŷ
oh, please tell me
we're gonna see the scorpion
fight that thing.
ź̳
cool grenade.
ĻѧϰϽҵ;
hello, my name is sam. have a nice day!
hello, my name is reaper. have a bad day!
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
reaper 206
-=Ļ=-
: У:
ʱ:󶬹ϻ
-=Ļ=-
: У:
ʱ:󶬹ϻ
ȳ
hi.
hey.
Ͼ
i'm getting up.
츮 ҷ?
what are we doin' today?
ڱ, 츮 ָ Բ ־ݾ
baby, we spent the whole
weekend together, every second.
˰ ־.
i know. it was amazing.
, ,
־, ׷
uh, i actually, uh, have some
errands to run today, so.
,
oh, cool. cool.
i like errands.
װ ģ ʿ ƴϾ
it's not really something
that i need company for.
׳ Ӹ ڸ
i'm just gonna get
my hair cut.
- ?
-...
- what else?
- uh...
Ƹ ؾ ž
probably gonna get
something to eat.
׷, . Դ
ok, cool. i like eating.
(Ƹ޸ī Ÿ) Դ ϴ?
do you like to eat llamas?
ֳĸ ִ 󸶸 Űŵ
'cause i'm gonna eat
a live llama.
׷, ڱ
ڱ ȥ ߰ڴ
ok, babe. you can
run your errands
by yourself today.
׳ ȭ
just call me
whenever you can.
, ڵ ٲϱ
oh, also, i took
the liberty of changing
your cellphone plan
츰 츮 Ҷ ־
so we can talk
to each other
whenever we want
츮 ϴ ŭ
for as long as we want.
߰ڴ
i gotta go.
-׷
- ok.
׷
ok.
,
ڱ. ˰?
unlimited minutes,
sweetie. ok?
̾ƾ
don't let 'em go to waste.
ϳ
nina.
⼭ ϴ ž?
what are you
doin' here?
...
= =
hey...
wondrous dove hollow
࿡ ?
did sam ask you to go
on this trip with him?
-
- ڰ ׷
- yeah.
- ben asked me to go, too.
հڴ, ׷?
it sounds like
a lot of fun, right?
Ⱦ
i don't really wanna go.
,  ؾ ?
oh, how should i tell him?
, ?
well, how come
you don't wanna go?
.. ̶ ʿ䰡 ־
i just--i need to be
away from ben right now.
ŵ
i'm a solitary creature.
ž?
is everything ok?
everything's great.
ben is great.
..
he's just--
״ ׻ ű־
he's always there
վ Ĵٺ鼭..
staring at me,
󸶳 Ƹٿ ϸ鼭..
telling me
how beautiful i am.
׸
ben is adorable, and i
really, really like him,
׷, ״
鷯پ ʾ
but, um, he's just
a little clingy--heh!
.
sometimes. kind of
makes me wanna
ְ Ͱ
rip out his internal organs
and show 'em to him.
˰ھ?
you know?
, ¥ ƴϰ..
׷ ˰?
i mean, not really
but you know what i mean.
, ׳ ھ
look, ben is just
a sensitive guy,
װ ƴϾ
which isn't a bad thing.
׳ ϰ
just be honest with him.
׷. ϰ..
right. honest.
׳ ڶ Ʈؾ ϳ
i guess i'm just used
to dating guys from hell,
˰ھ? ,
׵ ó ϰŵ
you know? i mean,
they treat you like crap,
׷  װ нŰݾ
but at least it's exciting.
, ׷ ϰ ִ ?
oh, but who am i talking to?
ڶ Ʈ ϴ ݾ
you know all about
dating bad boys.
, ڰ ƴϾ
uh, sam isn't exactly
a bad boy.
׷, ׷ Ƶݾ
ok, but he's
the son of the devil,
״ϱ..~ ״ ϰ ɰž
so--heh. mean, he's gotta
be a little bit evil.
׷? װ ڸ ̴ϱ
right? it's sort of
in his nature.
= ȯմϴ =
welcome to dove hollow
Ϻϴ
this place is perfect,
Ҹġ Ϻϴ
creepy perfect.
. 氡
mm. just like
the way i french.
׾־
this town is dead.
. 츰 ȣڿ
good. it means we got
our pick of rooms at the hotel.
?
wanna get
something to eat?
׷. װڴ
yes. i'm starving.
üũ Ϸ . ̸
let's go check in. come on.
. ,
ooh. oh,
look at this.
輼
hello.
ƹ ?
anybody home?
 帱?
how can i help you?
, 츰 ʿؿ
Ʋġ
uh, we need rooms
for 2 nights.
, ϳ ̶ ص
ϳ
um, one for sam and andi,
and one for ben...
׸, , ʶ , ׷ϱ..
and, uh, then there's
me and you, so...
, 3̿
oh, i only have
3 rooms upstairs,
ħ ϳ̰
each with one bed.
, ħ ϳ
ȵƳ׿
ah. oh, one bed.
that's unfortunate.
׷, , ƿ
ʸ ٸ ̾
but, uh, i-i'm ok
with it if you're
ok with it.
̺ ʴ´ٸ ̾,
only if you don't steal
the covers, big bro.
! ,
ah ha! no problems,
little sis.
̺ҵ ׼ ç
i'm gonna
snatch those covers
right off of you.
״. !
i'm gonna tickle you
all night. ha ha!
~ ̿
ahh. it's my sister.
Ļð غ ſ
the room should be ready
by suppertime.
κ ͺ ?
you two ever
been up this way?
, ׷ ׿
nope, but i
love it already.
, ̶ 꿡
well, you should
take your sister
to the silver mine.
ϰŵ
it's quite a sight.
ѹ 꿡 µ
i've never been
to a mine before.
let's go.
, ׷ ׷ Ƹ
uh, yeah. yeah, maybe.
輼
hello!
ʹ ̻ϴ
this is so weird.
-
-!
- oh.
- oh! hey.
Ŀ
帱?
good afternoon. can i
get you guys somethin'?
, . ġ 2
uh, yeah. can we get
a couple sandwiches?
ġŲ ɷ ּ
chicken for me, please.
, ɷ ҷ
yeah.
i'll have the same.
ݹ 帱Կ
comin' right up.
Ϳ ̴, ׷?
cute town, right?
-.....
-׷
- nnnn.
- yeah?
׳ ô ΰ?
just passin' through?
, , ƴϿ
ָ ӹ
uh, actually, no.
we're staying for the weekend,
õ ø  ְԿ
you know, getting
out of the city
for a while.
׷⿡
this is just the place
to do it,
Ƹٿ ϰſ
the most beautiful town
you'll ever see.
-մϴ
-ݾƿ
- thanks.
- you know what
- ӹô
ϼž ϴ Ƽ?
you guys should do
while you're here?
װ ?
what's that?
꿡
־
check out the mine
just up the hill.
츮 꿡 ϼ
you want us to go
to the mine?
absolutely.
װ 湮 κ
it's the best part
about visiting
dove hollow.
ű 𼭵 ſ
you'll never see
anything else like it.
ٷ ⿡ ־
ϽŴٸ
i have a map right here
if you'd like.
saloon.
ɾƼ
ϰ ־
i'm just sittin' here,
thinkin' about you.
ֱ ٷ
i hope you're doin' well.
ʵ ٵ..
i wish you were here.
ϰ ~~~ ;
i miss you soooo much.
Ű
smooch.
ģ ȭϴ ſ?
talkin' to your girl?
, ׳ ð ־
uh, just tryin' to get her
to come up here.
, ׳డ Եȴٸ
well, if she
makes it out here,
׳ฦ ž ؿ
you should take her up
to the old silver mine.
ڵ ű Ѵϴ
women love that place.
, ű⼭ ̵
 Ÿ ð ſ
well, you kids'll have
the time of your lives
up there.
,
hey, guys.
ٿ ϶ ߴ ˾?
you know what
the guy at the bar
just told me to do?
-?
-꿡
- what?
- visit the mine.
׷, Ĵ翡 ִ ڵ ׷ ߾
yeah, that's what the lady
in the diner said, too.
-!
-, ũƾ ?
- yo!
- hey, where's kristen?
ȭް ־
takin' a tinkle.
, Ҹġ ȣ
also, the, uh,
creepy hotel guy
츮 ̷ õ߾
is trying
to kill us,
츮 꿡 ϴ
told us to go down
to the mine.
츮׵ ־
same thing happened to us.
װͿ
the town's in on it.
׵ װ ̰ Ʋ
they must be
feeding it.
׷, 츰 ư ڴ
ok, we have to go right now.
ȥ Ѹ ִ ׸ ϳۿ ϱ
i only have a vessel
that can capture one soul.
ü ο
we can't fight
a whole town.
׸ϸ ƾ
good enough for me.
?
where's my car?
ٿ  ôµ
i saw it when i walked
into the bar.
we're trapped.
Ȱ -
dove hollow
sheriff - jail
ȳϼ. ,
Űϰ
hi. um, i'd like to
report a stolen car.
, ̺긮?
hippie car, hybrid?
װ Ƴ
it wasn't stolen.
߾
i had it towed.
ؼ
parked in a loading zone.
׷, ٽ ã ?
so, uh, when can
we get it back?
м Ұ ݾƼ
impound lot's
closed now.
ٽ ͺ
you could
try back tomorrow.
ȵſ, ȵſ. ,
ؼ
no, no. uh, we were
really hopin' to
hit the road today.
, 츮
׷ ϰ ?
well, what's your rush
to leave our little town?
Ƹٿ ݾ
it's a beautiful place,
󿡼 Ϻ ž
most perfect place
in the world.
̺~ ־
ø ӹ
come on. relax.
stay awhile.
Ƹٿ ϸ ־
we have
beautiful sunsets.
ݾ, 츮 ƹ
you know, my daddy
used to say
ϸ ϴ 󿡰 ڶ
Űϴ ٰ Ͻð ߰ŵ
sunset is like god
kissin' the world good night.
츮 ƹ ڼ
my daddy was a preacher,
ū ϴ,
big fire-and-brimstone,
end-of-the-world kind of guy.
ϴ?
- heh heh.
- you believe in hell?
, ..
uh, well, i--
𸣰ھ. ..
i don't really know.
um...
.. 翡 ϰ ;
i--i like to focus
on the here and now.
׷. ֵ ̰ ٰ
ok. you boys
enjoy your visit.
-
- yep.
- yeah.
= μ & ħ =
׷ ٽ ޼ ž
blue blossom bed & breakfast
so i'm leaving a message.
again.
, ..츰 ڸ
um, i--we're sorta
trapped here,
׷ ʾ
but i don't want you
to get worried.
ϰ ʹ,
; ߵھ
i really miss you,
and i can't wait to see you.
׷, ..ȭ ˰?
ok, c-call me. ok?
-,
-
- hey, ben.
- hey.
...
ben...
󸶳 ϳ ȭɾ?
how often would you say
you call nina?
. ε..
oh. depends.
2ð ƴϸ
every couple hours or...
ð
every hour
ƴϸ δ 30и
or sometimes
on the half-hour.
?
what?
׷, ݾ,
,
ok, you know, don't
take this the wrong way,
ֳĸ ϰ ϰ ٿ
ٰ ϰŵ
'cause i think it's great
that you're so attentive
and loving,
׷ ڵ ׳..
but sometimes
girls just need...
ʿ
space.
ϳ ž?
did she say
something to you?
, ݾ, 鷯ٴ´ٴ
޵Ǿ ž
well, you know,
the word "clingy"
might have come up.
鷯ٴ´ٰ?
鷯ٴ´?
clingy?
she called me clingy?
damn.
ȮϷ ȭؾ ڴ
i gotta call her
to make sure
everything's ok.
ȵ ȵ ȵ ȵ
׷ ̾
no. no, no, no.
you know what?
׳ ȭ⸦ ڴ
maybe we should
just turn this off
for a while.
⿣ ͳ ְ
there are miles and
miles of tunnels
Ʒ ó ž
and they're all
underneath the city.
ȥ ã Ұ Ұž
it's gonna be impossible
to find this thing.
װ ˾? ؾ
̰ û ̿
you know what? forget it.
this was a dumb idea.
츰 ȥ ž
we can't nab this thing now.
, Ƹ Ϸ
Ѿ
i mean, maybe i can
sweet-talk the devil
into letting this one go.
հ , ?
sweet-talk
the devil, huh?
, װ Ѱž?
i mean, you do that?
ƴϾ, ׷ ׷
not well, but i try.
...
hey...
񸶸?
thirsty?
ȣڿ Ծ
got it from the hotel.
ũĿ ԰
also i have some crackers.
, ݾ, ׳
̷ ƴ
sam, you know, i just
really don't think
this is the time.
ƴϾ, ƴϾ.
θƽ ָ ݾ
no, no. i promised you
a romantic weekend.
츮
there's no reason we can't
enjoy ourselves a little bit.
-...
-ٷ
- um...
- hold on.
ũṵ̃
no corkscrew.
Ƹ ׳ ̷ ..
maybe i could just do this.
ϴ ž?
what are you doing?
, ̷ ̻ Ǹ ŵ
every now and then,
i get this weird devil power.
װ
װ ൿ Ÿŵ
i can't really control it.
it usuallyops up
ȥ ̷ Ҷ ..
׷ غþ
when a soul is trying to
kill me, but i was thinkin'...
Ƹ .. õ ..
maybe i--i could...
try.
damn it.
?
what?
you're getting
pretty comfortable
̷ ſ ̾,
׷ ʴ?
with all of this,
aren't you?
ٴ ž?
comfortable with what?
ȥ ,
Ǹ
capturing souls,
devil powers.
ź Ƶ Ǵ ̾
i mean, being
the son of satan.
ϴ ž
what are you talking about?
ƴ, װ ׳..
׷ ó
no, it just--
it seems like
̷  ͵
̻ ʴ ó
none of this even
bothers you anymore.
ص,  ׷ ־?
andi, how can you say that?
, 츰 ó տ
ǳ ϰ ־
ok, we're having
a picnic in front of
a--a monster lair.
...
well...
ڴ
ϰ..
i have to wonder
if you're
׷ ŸϷ ..
getting sucked
into the lifestyle.
 Ϳ ž
i'm not getting sucked
into anything.
ñ
i have no choice.
ó 鸮 ϴµ,
that's starting to sound
like an excuse, sam.
-˰ ־
-?
- i knew it.
- what?
߾
װ
i thought
he would be cool
η ָ ϰ ٰ
and let me have
one decent weekend away.
-?
-
- who?
- the devil.
״ ׻ ġ
he's always screwing me.
װ ָ ɰŶ ׷
he promised
this great weekend,
׸ Ͼ
ٺ
and i actually believed him.
i'm an idiot.
-
-ȵ, . ̰ ʾ
- sam.
- no, damn it. this is not fair.
ϰ ׷ Ŵ?
did you just do that?
ƴ
no.
׷. ..
yeah. i don't--
𸣰ھ
i don't know.
׷, ݾ,
츮 ư ڴ
ok, you know, we should
just head back.
ħ Ͽ ؼ
̾
i'm so sorry about
the whole one-bed thing.
ȵ
that's nonsense.
׷, ,
츰 ž, ׷?
but, uh, i think
we'll make due, right?
-ȵ, ȵ!
-!
- no, no!
- ohh!
, ̾, ̾
oh, i'm sorry. sorry.
, ̾, ...
uh, sorry. uh...
, . ȿ
˾?
hey, look. in there,
you know what they don't have
츰 ʿ ž
that we need
is ice cubes.
ϰ
really badly.
ֳĸ ŵ
because i cannot drink
warm water.
ϰ 츱 ؼ ޶ ְڴ?
do you think maybe--
maybe you could go scrounge
a little up for us?
׷
ok.
Ʒ
downstairs.
õõ
take your time.
, ȵ, ȵ
oh, no, you don't.
ϰ ̷ ĥ
you are not
ruining this for me.
, ׷
oh, yeah.
ʹ, ħ?
ʹ?
you wanna fly, cot?
you wanna fly?
̸
come here. unh!
, ħ!
uhh! suck it, cot!
̽ ӽ
no ice machine.
? ,
what? ah, that's ok.
· ð̴
it's bedtime anyway.
Ҹ?
what's that noise?
Ҹ? .. 𸣰ھ
noise. i--i don't know.
, ..Ƹ ٸ 濡
ȭ ȭ ϳ
i, uh--maybe someone
havin' a phone conversation
in the other room.
 ͵
could be anything.
..׷ ..
d-don't--
⿡ ħ븦 ž?
did you throw
that cot down there?
? ?
׷ھ? װ..
what? why?
why would i? that's--
Ƴ Ƴ װ ģ ̾
no. no. that's crazy.
Ƿ ׷ ?
you did that on purpose
츮 ħ뿡 ڰ Ϸ
so that we'd have
to sleep together
in the same bed.
, ̾. ׷
mmm, true. yes.
׷ݾ
ٰŶ
you told me
you would protect me,
ְڴٰ
protect my virginity.
װ ׾
i was protecting it.
ڽ ؼ,
ϴ
for yourself, sock.
this is terrible.
׷ž? ?
is it? is it terrible?
𸣰ھ. ׷ , ũƾ
i don't know. i don't
think so, kristen.
, װſ ؼ غ
츮 ߴٴ ִ?
i mean, think about it.
c-can you deny that we
have a connection?
μ
a brother-and-sister
connection.
츰 ¥ ģô ƴݾ, ũƾ?
we're not actually
related, 'k, kristen?
ϰ  ٸ ٸ
 ͵ ݾ
i mean, if you had've
met me any other way,
doing anything,
츮 Ʈ ϴ ٸ,
like if we were
paintballing,
̺ ϴ ٸ,
۶̵ ϴ ٸ,
𸣰ھ
scuba diving,
hang gliding,
i don't know,
.. ٸ ž
you--you would think of
me in a different way.
admit it.
ƴ. ׷ ʾ ž
no. i would not.
׷. ...
ok. uh...
.. ̾ϴ
....
i'm--i'm really sorry.
i--i--
׷.
yeah. ok.
, ̾
uh, i'm sorry.
ڵ̶..
women.
װ ƿ...
̽׸
they're like a--
they're like a mystery
̽׸ ο..
wrapped inside
of a mystery
° ̽׸ ο..
wrapped inside of
a third mystery.
˰ھ?
you know what i mean?
unreal.
̰ 2 ּ
can i get 2 more of those?
, 𷯵 ֽðھ?
also, can i have
a wine cooler,
׷ װ ܿ ־ ּ
ڴ ̰Կ
but put it in a beer glass.
make it look extra manly.
ڴٿ ϳ
one manly wine cooler
comin' up.
ڸ ?
is this seat taken?
,
um, no.
ȳϼ, ũƾ̿
hi. i'm kristen.
׷, ˾
yeah, i know.
ȳϼ. ũƾ̿
hi. i'm kristen.
ȳ. ̾. ...
hi. i'm sock. what...
, ׷, ׷, ׷
ݸ ٷ
oh, wait, wait, wait.
wait a minute.
˰ڴ. ׷, ״ϱ..
츮 ó ô ϴ ?
i get it. ok, are--
are we pretending that
we're just meeting
..
ٿ 쿬 ó?
right now,
like randomly at the bar?
. ׷
. հڴ
i like it. ok.
i like it. that's hot.
, , ࿡ 츮
ٿ ٸ
uh, ok, if we were meeting
at the bar right now,
Ƹ ּ
ѵ ž
i would probably
try and pick you up
with my best line.
-
-׷
- ok.
ѵ
pick me up.
Ƿմϴ
excuse me.
-
-ȳϼ
- yes.
- hi.
Žñ⸦ ϴ ƿ
i think you're
standing on my penis.
ߴ
Ȯ
i'm not sure
i understand,
ŷ 鸮
but it sounds
charming.
...
well...
, ôµ
sock, i have
had thoughts,
ؼ ̾
thoughts about you.
о
Ģ Ű ߴ
i was raised to push
my feelings away
and follow rules,
׷ Ģ Ű ʾ
but you don't
follow rules.
Ģ ٺ ž
rules are for a-holes.
濡 ħ뵵
one bed in the room
will be fine.
all right.
* spending all our days *
츮
* in the valley of the sun *
¾ ¥⿡
, ̶ ũƾ ?
well, where are
sock and kristen?
׵鵵 츮 ˰ ִ ?
i mean, they know
we're leaving, right?
, ڰ ־,
oh, sleeping,
i guess.
εȴµ
i knocked
on their door,
and no one answered.
ð
wake 'em up.
i'm getting my car,
׸ ׷
and then we're getting
out of here right now.
츮
ž
the longer we stick around,
the more likely something
bad'll happen.
ȳ
mornin'.
ȳϼ. ...
mornin'. uh...
, , Ʒ ̿
hey, uh, we were just
comin' to see you
ã
so we could pay the fine
and get our car.
⼭ ־
ƴ ?
do you have any idea
what happened here?
µ
i do not.
, ʶ ģ
well, uh, since you
and your friends
ӹ ִ ̰ŵ
are the only ones
stayin' here, i'd say...
׷ ſ ۴ٰ
suspect pool,
pretty small.
ο
hello.
ħ, ģ
morning, friends.
Ȱ
sheriff.
̰ ħ?
sir, is this your cot?
ٵ ̿
you know what?
, ׷
ŰȽ
yeah, it is.
i don't care.
θ Ҹĥž
i'll shout it
from the rooftops.
ħ!
that is my cot!
! ƴϿ, ƴϿ!
ħ ƴϿ!
ow! no, no!
that is not my cot!
, ̾?
sock, what's going on?
ڻ ı߾
he vandalized
police property.
, ̷ ʿ ?
oh, is this
really necessary?
Ÿ ! 㿡
degenerate! last night,
ڱ ̶ ħ븦
he shared a bed
with his own sister.
ƴ, ƴϿ. Ǻ׵̿
no, no. stepsister.
װ װ
it's the same thing.
ƴϿ! , ׷ ʾƿ
no! really, it's not.
޽ !
you make me sick!
ƴ, ƴϾ, ޽ ʾ
no, no, not sick.
healthy.
ǰ ھ!
ʹ...
you're a very
healthy girl!
you are so--
츰 !
we are so healthy!
ģ ϳ ɰž
i'm gonna release
your buddy on wednesday.
װ, ...
that should, uh...
׿ ð ǰ
give him enough time
to learn his lesson.
, ..ϴ, Ȱ
׷
uh, th-thank you, sir.
yes.
ͱ
i wanna ask you
about somethin'.
ȥ μ
Żؼ ȥ
bureau of souls
escaped and missing souls
̰ ߰߾
i found that in your car.
װſ. , ׷
that. uh, yes.
, б ,
uh, it's a school
project, boring.
б
school project.
â ̿
creative writing class.
, ̰ڱ
well, that must be
a great class.
Ż ȥ,
escaped souls,
, ׸...
the devil, and a...
ٷ ϵ
hellish being right here
in dove hollow.
հڴµ
now, that's exciting stuff.
ϴ. ׷
thank you. yeah.
Ǿڸ ׷ , ׷?
if only a publisher felt
the same way, right?
˰,
־
you know,
you can trust me.
. .. ˰ ־. ׷Կ
yeah. i--i know. i do.
ٰ
i'll tell you
what i'm gonna do.
׷ ұϰ ٰž
i'm still gonna release
your car to you
ൿ ̾
鸮 ʴ?
as an act of good faith.
does that sound good?
׷׿. մϴ
yeah. thank you.
׷ ٽ ϰ ͱ
ϰ
but i wanna reiterate--
anything you wanna tell me,
ٴ ..
anything at all,
׻ ִ
door's always open.
, Ȱ. մϴ
yes, sir. thank you.
׷. 츮 ذؼ ڱ
ok. glad we got that
all cleared up.
⼭ ?
guess we're done here.
, ̽ ø
you're free to go,
mr. oliver.
մϴ
thank you.
ο ޼
no new messages
silent
׷, ԰ ־
ok, you keep eating.
you get yourself
nice and garlicky.
ݹ ð
i'll be back
in a little while.
, ãҾ
hey. got the car back.
?
what's the problem?
,
um, i'm leaving.
̻ ְھ
i can't stay here anymore.
i'll walk home.
ƴ, ϶ ӻѰ
no. no, she's upset
about sock.
ȵ ũƾ,
츮 ⿡ ӹ
no. kristen, we have
to stay here just
a little longer,
ö
until sock
gets out of jail.
ƴϾ, ٰ,
no, i'll take her, sam.
· ؾ ϵ ְ
i got a couple things
i gotta do anyway.
׷.
׷, ׷
yeah. all right.
yeah, yeah.
ʳ ư
you guys
should go back.
ũƾ, ö󰡼 ì ׷?
kristen, why don't
you go up and pack?
. ׷, ׷ ʳ
ok. yeah,
so you guys'll go ahead,
⼭ ɶ ٸ
and me and ben'll wait here
until sock gets released.
׷ ׷
guess so.
׷
ok.
̹ ָ ̾
i'm really sorry
this weekend
ʾƼ ̾
didn't turn out the way
it was supposed to.
װ ó ް ,
it was never gonna be
a vacation, sam.
ȥ ׻ 켱ϱ
the soul was always
your first priority.
ư ٽ
why don't we just talk
about this when i get back?
ž
i don't want you
to worry about me.
i'll be fine.
, ȵǴµ
mm, i'm not worried.
= ϴ =
now leaving dove hollow
ȳϼ?
͵帱?
afternoon.
can i help you?
ģ ã ־
i am looking
for my friends.
³ ϰŵ
they enjoy
alcoholic beverages,
׷ Ŷ ߾
so i thought
they might be here.
. , ¿
oh. uh, 3 guys,
2 girls,
«͵?
kind of
a funny bunch.
´ ׿
that sounds right.
ۿ ƴٴϰ ſ
believe they're
out and about,
׷ ⼭ ٸ
but you're welcome
to wait here.
ƿ.
great. thanks.
׳ ̳ Կ
i'll just have water.
ݹ
comin' right up.
, , Ⱥ?
hey, uh, you been out
to see the mine yet?
ѹ ѷ
should take a look.
ŵ
it's pretty amazing.
ƾ
Ϸ ° ƴϰŵ
no, thanks.
i'm not here to sightsee,
׳ ģ Ϸ
just surprising
my boyfriend.
. ׷ ģ 𸣳
oh. uh, so your friends
aren't expecting you.
nope.
׷ ƹ ִ 𸣰ڳ׿
so nobody knows
you're here, then.
Ƹ ׷
probably not.
ִµ
interestin'.
... ֳ׿
you're...off.
?
beg your pardon?
߸Ʊ
ƴϿ
something's wrong with you.
you're not real.
׸..
and--
you smell like hell.
׸ ִ ׿
and you smell delicious.
׷, ̾?
ũƾ ׳ ٰ?
so, really?
kristen just left?
ѷ ٰ?
she boogied out of here?
ؼ ȹ?
޼ ȳ?
did she ask about me?
did she send me a message?
-ӿ ѱ׳ ?
-!
- in a bottle or pigeon
or something?
- no!
츰 ؾ
⼭
we gotta focus, get you
the hell out of here.
ũ ־
we could
go shawshank.
ũ?
shawshank?
츮 ܴ ɴ ȿ 鿩
we smuggle in
a rock pick,
ž
and sock could dig
his way out.
װ ȭݾ,
that was a movie, ben.
å ž
it was based
on a book.
׷. װ 20 ɸ ʾҳ?
yeah. didn't it take him,
like, 20 years?
, 츮 20йۿ
you guys, we don't
have 20 minutes.
Ȱ ݹ ־
the sheriff could
be here any second.
¾. ׷
all right. ok.
׷ ڹ踦 ν
then we break
the lock.
old school.
׷, ̾?
yeah, what does that mean?
ٿ ð
i'm gonna go borrow
the pickax from the bar.
hey.
, ?
uh, i was wondering if
i could borrow something--
ſ
that.
Ϸ?
what do you need
that old thing for?
, .. ׳ Ұ ־
uh, j--i just need
to ax something.
̿, ׳ ̷ο
a hole, just for fun.
, ׷ ʳ׿
well, i'm not sure
that's such a good idea.
ǰ̰ŵ
that thing's
sort of an antique.
, ̰ ϳ ε
hey, this is
nina's purse.
, ģ ֳ?
hey, is my girlfriend here?
ݹ߿, Ƹ,
̳..
blonde, beautiful,
a little intimidating.
. ׿
yeah. think i saw her.
-...
-𰬴 𸣰ڳ׿
- ah...
- not sure where
she got off to.
׿
cool.
ٽ غϱ
on second thought,
ϱ
you can borrow my ax.
why, i trust you.
̸ ż
why don't you
come back here
and take it down.
thanks.
߾µ
i warned him,
ʳ
stay away from you guys.
ʴ
he just wouldn't listen.
ȥ ؿ
i've been all alone
with this thing
10 Ǿ
goin' on 10 years now.
that's when people
started disappearin'.
׳ ƴϿ
they didn't
just disappear.
װ ſ
that thing ate them,
׸ ȥ ſ
and you
fed them to it.
, ñ
well, i had no choice.
ִ ߾
ؼ ̾
i did everything i could
to stop people from comin' here.
Ұ
i drove the locals out.
.. ü з ఴ ¾
i--i turned away
whole busloads of tourists.
now look at this place.
̾
it's a ghost town.
ġä ־
i've noticed.
װ ߱ ⿡ ٸ
if i'm notere
to stop it,
׷ٸ , ֿ
ž
then it might go on
to the next town,
the next state.
, ׷ ƴ?
i mean, do you have
any idea what it's like
Ȳ ̾
to be stuck in a situation
ϰ ϰ ؾϴ..
where you have to do
something you don't wanna do
and there's no way out?
׷. Ȯ ˰ڳ׿
 Ȳ..
yeah. i know exactly
what that's like.
, ִ װǰ?
um, is everybody
in the town that thing?
׵ ˼ ֳ?
i mean, are they
all tentacles?
׷
yeah.
װ.. װ 䳻,
it--it mimics people,
װ ̳ó
and it uses them
like fishing lures,
׸ ׷ θ Դ
and then it takes
everybody up in the mine
where it feeds.
׷ Ȱ
츮 ϼ̳?
so why'd you decide
to help us now?
Ǹ о
when i read
your devil folder,
ϰ ؼ ٰ
i figured maybe you
were sent to help.
װ ߾ݾ
i told you what it was.
ϰ
now you tell me
what you are.
ģ ݾ
i saved your friend's life.
Ȱ
everything you saw
in that folder,
¥
it's for real.
ȥ ƿ
i catch souls
for the devil,
Ż ȥ̿
souls that have
escaped from hell,
꿡 ִ ȥó
like the one
in your mine here.
ű⼭ Ż ֳ?
has anyone
escaped from it?
, Ƹ װ..
i mean, maybe it--
that thing
ϳ ٷ ʾ ݾƿ
didn't eat nina right away.
, ƴϾ. ̾ϴ,
oh, no. sorry, son.
Կ Դ´ܴ
takes everything
in one big gulp
׳ ž, ׷?
think she went down
swiftly, right?
ȭ ۵ɶ ..
till digestion starts.
ϰ Ѵٸ
ȹ ֱ ٶ
if you're workin' for the devil,
hope you got a plan.
. װ ǵ ſ
yeah. i'm gonna
send it back to hell...
̰ɷ
with this.
, װ.. װ ׳ װ ȭԸ Ұž
well, that--that's just
gonna make it angry.
̰ ź ƴϿ
̰ ׸̿
it's not
a normal grenade.
it's a vessel.
ȥ ⿡ Ÿ ſ
i just need to get
close enough to the
soul to catch it.
׷
ok.
nice.
 ˰
you know, i think
i know how i can help.
?
gas?
, ȥ ٷο װ ã
well, the tricky thing about
this creature is findin' it,
׷ ǿ״ϱ
so i'm gonna
smoke it out.
Ա ־
you're gonna be
at the mine entrance.
װ ʿ ٰ
i'm gonna drive it to you.
̿
good idea.
ȳ?
do you smell smoke yet?
ִ ũƾ ̾
all i can smell
is kristen.
׳ ٴҶ Ҿ,
she was like
vanilla, boys.
ٴҶ
vanilla.
-̰ ʹ ɸ
-׷
- this is takin' too long.
- yeah.
-ĳھ
-ٷ! ȵ, !
- screw it.
- wait! no, ben!
ü ϴ ž?
what the hell
you doin', man?
׳డ ׾
ϳ ׾ٰ
she's dead.
nina's dead.
i have nothing
to live for.
óҰ
don't worry.
i'll take care of
this thing myself.
ȵ! , ƾ?
no! ben, you're
being crazy. come on.
⼭ ɰž
! , !
you're gonna
get eaten in there.
listen! hey, listen!
ϳ Ʈ, , 3 Ƴ?
you were dating nina
for, what, like 3 weeks?
, , Ҿ
i, on the other hand,
just lost a sister
and a lover.
츮 Բ Ѵٸ,
μ غϰ
i think if we stick
together, we can make it
װ ž
?
through this as a team,
you know what i mean?
ƴ. ׹ۿ  ã ž
no. i'm not gonna
find anyone else.
ٴٿ ־
there are plenty
of fish in the sea.
߿ ʾ
doesn't matter.
,
ϰھ?
i mean,
who's gonna want me?
Ǿ ȸ ž,
you bite your
tongue, benjamin.
Ծȿ ǰ
you bite your tongue
till it bleeds in your mouth.
Ƹٿ ھ
you are
a beautiful man,
ܸ鵵 鵵
on the outside
and the inside.
.. ݾ
you got that--
װ ȯϰ
that lights up the room.
- , װ ̾
-¾
- that laugh, that
infectious laugh.
- yeah.
׸ ƾ ݾ
and then you got
that sexy latin gaze
װ ڼ
that just pulls
you in like a magnet
from the mother ship.
.. ̾?
you...mean that?
ڹ ĳ ䷹ ߷
benjamin casper
perez gonzalez,
ĥ ӿ Ÿ ־
i could get lost
in your eyes for days.
ű⿡ ؼ ž
i'm not gonna
apologize for that.
¾
you're right.
װ ʾ
i don't wanna die.
,
i'm comin' down,
guys.
!
ha ha ha!
let's go.
! Ƹٿ !
aah! beautiful ben!
, ~
oh, my god.
hey.
benji.
츮 س¾
ȥ Ҿ
we did it.
we got the soul.
׸ ʿ
and you're welcome.
Ϳ.
wow. heh heh.
, ̰
now, this is
a surprise.
.. ?
wh-what is?
, ߴµ
well, i really
didn't think,
, ٽ Ŷ..
uh, i'd see
you guys again.
ſ, , ſ
i'm just very, uh,
very surprised.
ʾұ
you didn't set the fire.
, ȱ׷
no, i didn't.
, ȥ Ŷ ߾
in fact, i warned that thing
that you were comin'.
ߴٰ?
you what?
׷, ..
yeah, well--heh heh.
ȥ ˰ ־
it knew you were comin',
׷, , ̰屸
and, uh,
you guys won out.
׿ְ ϳ
you guys are damn good.
׷̾?
why would
you do that?
˰ ׵ ģ̰ ̾
you see, these are
my friends, my family.
,
õ ϸ
this little town,
this little slice of heaven
󿡼 ξ
is everything
i have in this world.
ݾ, и ƮؿԾ
you know, i been
datin' millie goin' on,
, 6 Ƴ
uh, 6 years now.
˼ Ѵٰ?
dude, you're bangin'
a tentacle?
, и ؼ ׷
please, don't talk
about millie like that.
ݾ
that's crude.
Ȱ, Ʊ
sheriff,
you're crazy.
, ƴ.
oh, here we go. good.
ٽ, ȭ Ⱦ
you see,
i don't like change.
ϰ ܼϰ ϰ ;
i like to keep things
pure and simple.
-..
-׸ װ ִ
- uh...
- and the way i see it,
ϱ
׿ Ѵٸ
if somebody has to die
to preserve my way of life,
װ õ
that's the price of paradise.
Ƴ
i must be crazy.
ϴ شٴ
forgot to load
the damn thing.
franco
츮 ó ɾֳ
we're sitting ducks.
° ?
what are we gonna do?
پ. 츰 ž
let's run
for the car. we can make it.
׷,
ʿ䰡 ־
ok, good.
we need a distraction.
, پ
benji, you run that way,
ġó Ҹ
װ ʸ Ѱ
scream like a maniac.
he chases you.
츮 ٽ , ͼ
ƿͼ ʸ Ұ
we go back, get the car,
come back around,
and rescue you. break.

װ ڻݾ
that stupid.
that's suicide.
, ?
 ģ
ڻҷ ߾ݾ
oh, what? you're willing
to kill yourself
over some chick,
ٵ ģ ؼ
ٴ ų
but you don't
sacrifice yourself
for your buddies?
׷. װ..װ ̴
ok. th-that's
a good point.
ƴ, ƴ, ƴ, ƴ, ƴϾ!
װ ̾
no, no, no, no, no!
that's a terrible point.
츰 Բ
we gotta go together.
-
- ž!
- shotgun.
- it's gonna be locked!
ƴ! â а ݾ
no, man! the windows
are wide open!
谡 !
ϴµ 谡 ž!
no keys! i'll bet
there's no keys!
,
what's with
the negative energy now, ben?
-ѷ! ѷ! ѷ! ѷ!
-, !
- hurry! hurry!
hurry! hurry!
- oh, my god!
谡 ?
where's the keys? oh.
ok.
ѷ!
ٷ!
hurry!
hold on!
ձ̾!
way ahead of you!
... ۵̺ , !
uh...
put her in hyperdrive, sammy!
װ ڳʿ ־, 츰
around his
corner, and we're
out of here.
keep going.
, , , !
, , !
go, go, go, go!
go, go, go!
,
oh, my god.
!
split up!
پ. پ, پ, پ
run. run, run, run.
,
oh, sammy.
ī޶ ȹٷ
you're lookin'
right in the camera.
'4 ' 𸣳?
( ̿ ϴ )
you ever hear
of the fourth wall?
Ȱ 츮 ̷ ؿ
the sheriff's
tryin' to kill us.
׷, ׿ Ϻ
yeah, him and
his perfect town.
̺ ġ ȭ
just like
a david lynch movie.
ʿؿ
i need somethin'
to defend myself.
, ̰ͻ̾
well, all i have
is this.
ȵſ! ..װ ׸ݾƿ!
װ ״
no! th-that's a vessel!
it doesn't work on people!
̰ ٴ
ī
it's more of
a bargaining chip
..
than a weapon,
actually.
׷ װ ϰ ξ
but it's
all you've got.
̰ ܿ ,
there is a way
out of this, sam,
׸ װ ٷ ⼭
and it starts
right here.
Ǵٸ Ƹٿ
another beauty
of this town..
ʴٴ
not a lot of places
to hide.
ٷ!
wait!
ٽ ؿ?
you want your town back?
ģ ϳ?
׵ ־
you want your friends,
they all still exist.
׵ ⿡ ־,
׸ ׵ ٽ Ǯ ־
i put 'em in here, and
i can let 'em out again.
ֱ
aren't you just
full of surprises?
. µ
ok. just let it out,
׷
and then
i'll let you go.
Ⱥ ?
you're not
gonna let me go.
Ƹ ׷
aw, probably not.
׷ ٰ
but i can
make it quick,
ƴϸ ų
or i can
draw it out.
޷Ⱦ
it's up to you.
̺
̷ ʿ
come on.
you don't have to do this.
ȥڼ
׷ ð ݾƿ
you spent so many years
alone with that monster.
װ ġ ſ
it'd drive anybody crazy.
.. ٽ ¥ ־
you can--you could have
a real life again.
׳ ָ
you just gotta walk away.
ȥ ,
̴,
wiout that creature,
without this town,
ȥڰ ɰž
i'd be all alone.
װ ĥ ־
ģ ;
you can get past that,
make new friends.
Ȱ, ȥκ
ȣϷ ϴ ־
sheriff, there was a time
when you tried to protect
people from this thing.
Ƿ ߴ ˰ ־
i know you used
to be a good person.
ٽ ׷ ־
you can be that again.
ƴ. ׶ ķ ʹ ߸ ؿԾ
no. i've done
too many bad things
since then.
̻ ߿ ʾ
doesn't matter
anymore.
ƹ͵ ׷ ʾ
nothin' does.
װ ϰ
which is why
you'd really
ؾ ϴ
better do what i say.
ü ̾?
what the hell happened?
𸣰ڳ׿
i don't know.
ooh. oh my ... help.
ϳ?
nina?
-ϳ, ׷! ȵ!
-!
- nina, don't! no!
- help me!
׸
don't kill him!
״ ȥ ƴϾ
̾
he's not a soul.
he's a person.
ϳ,
?
nina, come on.
all right?
׸ δ Ȥ ɰž
keep him alive is going to be way worse
츮 ׿ ִ  ó ̾
than any punishment
we can give him.
״ װ ؿԴ ó ư ž
he'll have to live
with what he did.
״ ȥڰ ž
he'll be all alone.
!
help me!
׷, ׷, ϰ
׸ ʹٸ
but, yeah, if you
just wanna throw him,
׷
you can do that, too.
׷ ȭ ƴϱ
so you're
indigestible.
иϰ
apparently.
ȥ ó 3 ־
that thing had
3 stomachs, like a cow.
ù° ͵ ߾
i never made it
past the first one.
׷ Ż̿
nice exfoliation,
though.
~ ߵƴ
ah. good for you.
˰ڴ
i get it.
˾?
get what?
ϰ ׸ ˰ھ
i get why you let him live.
װ ޱ ϴ
you want him to suffer.
ƴϾ. ״ ư ߾
ֳĸ ̴ϱ
no. he gets to live
because he's a human being.
츰 ʾ
we don't kill
human beings.
׷ ž
׷ ݾ
but his existence
will be terrible.
you said so yourself.
״ ޴ ӿ
ư ɰž
he's gonna live a life
of excruciating pain
װ ɰž
and touture.
it'll be hell on earth.
ؾǹ
you're diabolical.
ƴϾ, ׷ ʾ
װ Ƕ θ ž, ϳ
no, i'm not.
it's called
justice, nina.
״ ׷ž
he did it to himself.
ƴ, ׷
no, you are.
you're evil.
װ ſ ŷ
i find that
very attractive.
! ڱ
ڱ ?
benji! sweetheart,
are you here?!
ϳ
nina.
ϳ, ڱ,
.. ־
nina, baby,
y-you're alive.
ڱ
baby.
. ־
you're ok. you're alive.
˰ ־
ϰ ٴ ˰ ־
i knew it.
i knew you'd be ok.
ʹ ູ, ڱ
i'm so happy, baby.
ӻ̴ ž?
why are we whispering?
ڱ, ŵ
baby,
sock fell asleep.
hey.
ٷ. ׷.
wait. ok. all right.
.. ׳
you can't--you can't
just ignore me.
츮 ̰ſ ؼ ؾ
we have to talk
about this.
ٷ, ٷ!
ũƾ, ٷ
wait, wait!
kristen, hold on.
㿡 ־
what--what happened
the other night,
װ ̿
that was a good thing.
װ Ƹ ڿ
that was a beautiful,
natural thing.
ũƾ, ,
kristen, look at me,
please.
׷, ϰ ϱ ٶ
ok, i want you
to just tell me
ϰ ϴ ̾, ˰ھ?
what you're thinking
right now, ok?
ϰ..
be honest. it's ok.
ġ
i feel ashamed.
ġ?
ashamed?
. װ ̾?
oh. was it because
of that sweet-ass,
㿡 ߴ
crazy move that i did
the other night?
װ.. װ ġ ƴϾ
that--that is nothin'
to be ashamed of.
 ڶ ž
you don't understand
how i was raised.
ȭ
you don't understand
my culture,
󸶳 ġ ..
how powerful shame is.
˰ھ, ׷. ¾
.
ok, yeah. you're right.
i don't. i don't.
ȭ
i don't understand
your culture.
׷ װ ־
ȭ 
but i do understand
that it created
Ƹ, ȶϰ, մ
a beautiful,
smart, funny girl,
· ̱ ִ
a girl who is
in america now,
by the way,
ġɿ ؼ ణ ɵ
ʴ
a country that
doesn't give a rat's ass
about shame.
װ Ϻ ȭ 浹 ž
it's kind of like
the perfect clash
츰 ⿡ ؾ
of cultures
we got goin' on here.
ġ, ġɾ...
shame, shamelessness...
Բ ϸ 𰡸 âҰž
comin' together
to create somethin'
ٸ ִ ͺ
ξ ..
more sexy than anybody
could ever imagine.
¾
you're right.
츮 ̰ ıϰ ž
i will not allow my country
to ruin this.
Ȯ
exactly.
츮 濡
let's go to our room.
߱
پö. 
you got it.
hop on. come on.
ű
we're goin' there.
~
hey!
ȳ, Ʈ
hello, bert.
ȳϼ
hi.
ũƾ
kristen.
ȳϼ
hi.
׷, ģ
so, it looks like you two
have become friends.
츰..
we...
Ʋ ׷
certainly have.
츰.. ..
we were, uh...
׳ 츮 ̿
ۿ Ÿ ϴ,
just on our way
outside to play horsie,
ߴܹϰſ, Ƹ
do a little roughhousing,
maybe.
𸣰ھ. Ʈ ̿
i don't know. lawn darts.
. ,
heh. come on, sis.
let's go.
׷!
ok!
, ģ
hey, buddy.
. Ͻô ?
oh. what do you want?
, ׳ ߴٰ ַ
oh, just to tell you
you did a great job.
̿µ
Ǳϰ ֳ
it was a tough one,
but you came through
with flying colors.
ڽ ƿ ʸ
ʹ ڴ
i'm so pleased to see you
coming into your own.
׷, ,
帮׿!
yeah, well, thanks for
setting me up
ָ ޾ 糭
Ƴ־ ּż
for a train wreck
of a weekend getaway.
󸶳
Ұϰ ؼ
 ̶ ־?
do you have any idea
how impossible you've
made my life?
ص ũ ȭ
andi is furious with me,
׸ ׳  ȸؾ 𸣰ھ
and i don't know how
to make it up to her.
, ְ ͱ
sam, i wanna tell you
that i don't put you
ʸ ƴ϶ ..
in harm's way
just to get my jollies.
̷ Ȳ óϰ
ڽŰ ֱ ̾
i put you
in these situations because
i have confidence in you.
ο ڽŰ
i want you to have
confidence in yourself.
. װ
oh. that's great.
׸ ϰ ִµ
and i also wanna tell you
ϰ ˰ ִ ξ ٷ ־
you can handle much more
than you realize.
 ߵ
you can withstand any blow,
 ̾
any blow.
Ͻô ſ?
what are you
talking about?
µ, ƿԱ
didn't realize
you were back.
, ׷. .. ͼ ã ־
uh, yeah. i--i was just
about to come and find you.
̹ ָ ؼ ϰ ;
i wanna apologize
for this weekend.
鿡
, ̾
it got messed up
in a lot of ways,
and i'm really, really sorry.
׷ ..
츮 װ ٽ õؾ Ѵٰ
but i--i think
we should try it again.
ݾ, ʶ
you know,
just you and me,
츰 Ǵٸ ָ
ִ ?
we take another long weekend.
h-how about this next week?
׷
i can't.
ٷ. ̾?
Ŵݾ
wait. what do you mean?
you're the manager now.
׳ ݸ ϸ ݾ
just rework the schedule
a little.
, ̷ ȹ
sam, i can't make plans
for the future,
ʶ ƴϾ
not with you.
?
what?
ݾ, ϰ ݾ
you know, evil has
worked its way
κ ͼ ̾
into every part
of your life.
, ,
װ ѷΰ ִٴ
i mean, every day,
it surrounds you--
Ǹ,
demons, hell.
ϰ װ ϱ ߴٰ
ϴ
i can't help
but think that you're
starting to like it...
װ ϰ ϰ ־
that it's changing you.
Ƹ װ ȿ ־
m-maybe it's
always been in you.
װ ..
i just never saw it.
̾,
i'm sorry, sam.
̾
i'm really,
really sorry.
ص, ٷ
andi, wait.
ڴ ž?
are you
breaking up with me?
Ļ
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
ӭ
Ļ
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
ӭ